=No.9 Hunter=
=Episode 2=
Any demon slain by a Hunter
turns into Demon Essence
and is sealed within this token.
Essence is ranked from one to nine.
The Demon Hunting Bureau ranks you up
based on the Essence you collect.
This demon can be your entrance exam.
Yuanlang.
Hungry again?
This ghost chef's not bad!
Come on, come on!
Eat, eat, eat.
That's all you do, you glutton.
- Eat up. Let's go.
- Let's go.
Wait for your lovable and hungry senior!
(Longevity)
He...
was scared to death?
Don't be afraid.
The demonic energy is thick here.
The demon is still nearby.
(Watch me fool you.)
(This time I'll definitely eat you.)
This is a Love Demon.
A hopeless romantic, too.
It won't show itself
unless it sees a wedding ceremony.
Love Demon?
I come from the Void Realm.
I know every demon.
This demon envies those
who have true love
and tries to hurt them.
That's why it only preys on newlyweds.
Something's off.
The groom's clothes
and the wedding dress are here.
But where's the bride?
The demon must have taken her.
The Love Demon killed the groom
and took the bride
to practice some dark magic.
If we want to rescue the bride,
we need to hold a wedding ceremony
to lure it out.
A wedding ceremony?
Young Taoist.
Have you ever been married?
N-No, I haven't.
What are you planning?
(Longevity)
Darling.
Yuanchu is still young.
He knows nothing of romance.
Why didn't she pick me as the groom?
Ridiculous.
It's all just an act.
Catching the demon is what matters.
It's so good.
In your mortal world,
should I call you...
Husband?
Or perhaps...
Darling?
Or...
My beloved?
These are things married couples do.
What we're doing...
isn't right.
Oh.
I'll take responsibility for you.
Don't waste a night like this.
Young Taoist, you can't escape.
You pesky Taoist! You... I...
You've turned into a man?
(Whose face is this?)
Did he affect
the Stone Curse
and reverse my Yin and Yang?
Are you poison or cure?
I don't want to be a man!
Turn me back!
You have to have a way!
Actually...
this isn't that bad.
Makes things easier on the road.
It must be the Spirit-Calling Art
gone wrong.
Let me try it on you again.
Maybe that'll fix it.
Spirit-Calling Art?
What did you do to me?
Man to man. No touching.
Back off.
Keep your distance.
(Longevity)
(On Ghost Festival night,
a bride is wed.)
(Her kinfolk weep as tears are shed.)
(In paper red, she's for the dead.)
(Her living groom,
she'll never see again.)
That's not the demon's true form.
It's the Deceit Beast!
Deceit Beast?
You said it was a Love Demon.
No time to explain!
Just turn me back first!
Kiss me first!
Kiss me! Hurry!
(On Ghost Festival night,
a bride is wed.)
(Her kinfolk weep as if she's dead.)
(Longevity
In paper red, she's for the dead.)
(Her living groom,
she'll never see again.)
Break.
The Deceit Beast has powerful illusions
but weak demonic power.
You've harmed innocent villagers,
committing all kinds of evil.
Return the bride you took, now.
There are no innocents in this village.
Just like them,
both of you deserve to die!
A barrier.
It must be moving brides through
every household's well.
Young Taoist.
Stay close.
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away
this heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled paths
that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down,
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter
the hollow fate they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪